<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>St. John on Bible</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/</link><description>Recent content in St. John on Bible</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chapter 1</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/001/</guid><description>In the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the Word was God. The same was in the beginning with God. All things were made by him; and without him was not any thing made that was made. In him was life; and the life was the light of men. And the light shineth in darkness; and the darkness comprehended it not. There was a man sent from God, whose name was John.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 2</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/002/</guid><description>And the third day there was a marriage in Cana of Galilee; and the mother of Jesus was there: And both Jesus was called, and his disciples, to the marriage. And when they wanted wine, the mother of Jesus saith unto him, They have no wine. Jesus saith unto her, Woman, what have I to do with thee? mine hour is not yet come. His mother saith unto the servants, Whatsoever he saith unto you, do it.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 3</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/003/</guid><description>There was a man of the Pharisees, named Nicodemus, a ruler of the Jews: The same came to Jesus by night, and said unto him, Rabbi, we know that thou art a teacher come from God: for no man can do these miracles that thou doest, except God be with him. Jesus answered and said unto him, Verily, verily, I say unto thee, Except a man be born again, he cannot see the kingdom of God.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 4</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/004/</guid><description>When therefore the LORD knew how the Pharisees had heard that Jesus made and baptized more disciples than John, (Though Jesus himself baptized not, but his disciples,) He left Judaea, and departed again into Galilee. And he must needs go through Samaria. Then cometh he to a city of Samaria, which is called Sychar, near to the parcel of ground that Jacob gave to his son Joseph. Now Jacob&amp;rsquo;s well was there.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 5</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/005/</guid><description>After this there was a feast of the Jews; and Jesus went up to Jerusalem. Now there is at Jerusalem by the sheep market a pool, which is called in the Hebrew tongue Bethesda, having five porches. In these lay a great multitude of impotent folk, of blind, halt, withered, waiting for the moving of the water. For an angel went down at a certain season into the pool, and troubled the water: whosoever then first after the troubling of the water stepped in was made whole of whatsoever disease he had.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 6</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/006/</guid><description>After these things Jesus went over the sea of Galilee, which is the sea of Tiberias. And a great multitude followed him, because they saw his miracles which he did on them that were diseased. And Jesus went up into a mountain, and there he sat with his disciples. And the passover, a feast of the Jews, was nigh. When Jesus then lifted up his eyes, and saw a great company come unto him, he saith unto Philip, Whence shall we buy bread, that these may eat?</description></item><item><title>Chapter 7</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/007/</guid><description>After these things Jesus walked in Galilee: for he would not walk in Jewry, because the Jews sought to kill him. Now the Jews&amp;rsquo; feast of tabernacles was at hand. His brethren therefore said unto him, Depart hence, and go into Judaea, that thy disciples also may see the works that thou doest. For there is no man that doeth any thing in secret, and he himself seeketh to be known openly.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 8</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/008/</guid><description>Jesus went unto the mount of Olives. And early in the morning he came again into the temple, and all the people came unto him; and he sat down, and taught them. And the scribes and Pharisees brought unto him a woman taken in adultery; and when they had set her in the midst, They say unto him, Master, this woman was taken in adultery, in the very act. Now Moses in the law commanded us, that such should be stoned: but what sayest thou?</description></item><item><title>Chapter 9</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/009/</guid><description>And as Jesus passed by, he saw a man which was blind from his birth. And his disciples asked him, saying, Master, who did sin, this man, or his parents, that he was born blind? Jesus answered, Neither hath this man sinned, nor his parents: but that the works of God should be made manifest in him. I must work the works of him that sent me, while it is day: the night cometh, when no man can work.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 10</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/010/</guid><description>Verily, verily, I say unto you, He that entereth not by the door into the sheepfold, but climbeth up some other way, the same is a thief and a robber. But he that entereth in by the door is the shepherd of the sheep. To him the porter openeth; and the sheep hear his voice: and he calleth his own sheep by name, and leadeth them out. And when he putteth forth his own sheep, he goeth before them, and the sheep follow him: for they know his voice.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 11</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/011/</guid><description>Now a certain man was sick, named Lazarus, of Bethany, the town of Mary and her sister Martha. (It was that Mary which anointed the Lord with ointment, and wiped his feet with her hair, whose brother Lazarus was sick.) Therefore his sisters sent unto him, saying, Lord, behold, he whom thou lovest is sick. When Jesus heard that, he said, This sickness is not unto death, but for the glory of God, that the Son of God might be glorified thereby.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 12</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/012/</guid><description>Then Jesus six days before the passover came to Bethany, where Lazarus was, which had been dead, whom he raised from the dead. There they made him a supper; and Martha served: but Lazarus was one of them that sat at the table with him. Then took Mary a pound of ointment of spikenard, very costly, and anointed the feet of Jesus, and wiped his feet with her hair: and the house was filled with the odour of the ointment.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 13</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/013/</guid><description>Now before the feast of the passover, when Jesus knew that his hour was come that he should depart out of this world unto the Father, having loved his own which were in the world, he loved them unto the end. And supper being ended, the devil having now put into the heart of Judas Iscariot, Simon&amp;rsquo;s son, to betray him; Jesus knowing that the Father had given all things into his hands, and that he was come from God, and went to God; He riseth from supper, and laid aside his garments; and took a towel, and girded himself.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 14</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/014/</guid><description>Let not your heart be troubled: ye believe in God, believe also in me. In my Father&amp;rsquo;s house are many mansions: if it were not so, I would have told you. I go to prepare a place for you. And if I go and prepare a place for you, I will come again, and receive you unto myself; that where I am, there ye may be also. And whither I go ye know, and the way ye know.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 15</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/015/</guid><description>I am the true vine, and my Father is the husbandman. Every branch in me that beareth not fruit he taketh away: and every branch that beareth fruit, he purgeth it, that it may bring forth more fruit. Now ye are clean through the word which I have spoken unto you. Abide in me, and I in you. As the branch cannot bear fruit of itself, except it abide in the vine; no more can ye, except ye abide in me.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 16</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/016/</guid><description>These things have I spoken unto you, that ye should not be offended. They shall put you out of the synagogues: yea, the time cometh, that whosoever killeth you will think that he doeth God service. And these things will they do unto you, because they have not known the Father, nor me. But these things have I told you, that when the time shall come, ye may remember that I told you of them.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 17</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/017/</guid><description>These words spake Jesus, and lifted up his eyes to heaven, and said, Father, the hour is come; glorify thy Son, that thy Son also may glorify thee: As thou hast given him power over all flesh, that he should give eternal life to as many as thou hast given him. And this is life eternal, that they might know thee the only true God, and Jesus Christ, whom thou hast sent.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 18</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/018/</guid><description>When Jesus had spoken these words, he went forth with his disciples over the brook Cedron, where was a garden, into the which he entered, and his disciples. And Judas also, which betrayed him, knew the place: for Jesus ofttimes resorted thither with his disciples. Judas then, having received a band of men and officers from the chief priests and Pharisees, cometh thither with lanterns and torches and weapons. Jesus therefore, knowing all things that should come upon him, went forth, and said unto them, Whom seek ye?</description></item><item><title>Chapter 19</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/019/</guid><description>Then Pilate therefore took Jesus, and scourged him. And the soldiers platted a crown of thorns, and put it on his head, and they put on him a purple robe, And said, Hail, King of the Jews! and they smote him with their hands. Pilate therefore went forth again, and saith unto them, Behold, I bring him forth to you, that ye may know that I find no fault in him.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 20</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/020/</guid><description>The first day of the week cometh Mary Magdalene early, when it was yet dark, unto the sepulchre, and seeth the stone taken away from the sepulchre. Then she runneth, and cometh to Simon Peter, and to the other disciple, whom Jesus loved, and saith unto them, They have taken away the LORD out of the sepulchre, and we know not where they have laid him. Peter therefore went forth, and that other disciple, and came to the sepulchre.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 21</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/st.-john/021/</guid><description>After these things Jesus shewed himself again to the disciples at the sea of Tiberias; and on this wise shewed he himself. There were together Simon Peter, and Thomas called Didymus, and Nathanael of Cana in Galilee, and the sons of Zebedee, and two other of his disciples. Simon Peter saith unto them, I go a fishing. They say unto him, We also go with thee. They went forth, and entered into a ship immediately; and that night they caught nothing.</description></item></channel></rss>