<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Exodus on Bible</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/</link><description>Recent content in Exodus on Bible</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chapter 1</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/001/</guid><description>Now these are the names of the children of Israel, which came into Egypt; every man and his household came with Jacob. Reuben, Simeon, Levi, and Judah, Issachar, Zebulun, and Benjamin, Dan, and Naphtali, Gad, and Asher. And all the souls that came out of the loins of Jacob were seventy souls: for Joseph was in Egypt already. And Joseph died, and all his brethren, and all that generation. And the children of Israel were fruitful, and increased abundantly, and multiplied, and waxed exceeding mighty; and the land was filled with them.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 2</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/002/</guid><description>And there went a man of the house of Levi, and took to wife a daughter of Levi. And the woman conceived, and bare a son: and when she saw him that he was a goodly child, she hid him three months. And when she could not longer hide him, she took for him an ark of bulrushes, and daubed it with slime and with pitch, and put the child therein; and she laid it in the flags by the river&amp;rsquo;s brink.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 3</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/003/</guid><description>Now Moses kept the flock of Jethro his father in law, the priest of Midian: and he led the flock to the backside of the desert, and came to the mountain of God, even to Horeb. And the angel of the LORD appeared unto him in a flame of fire out of the midst of a bush: and he looked, and, behold, the bush burned with fire, and the bush was not consumed.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 4</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/004/</guid><description>And Moses answered and said, But, behold, they will not believe me, nor hearken unto my voice: for they will say, The LORD hath not appeared unto thee. And the LORD said unto him, What is that in thine hand? And he said, A rod. And he said, Cast it on the ground. And he cast it on the ground, and it became a serpent; and Moses fled from before it.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 5</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/005/</guid><description>And afterward Moses and Aaron went in, and told Pharaoh, Thus saith the LORD God of Israel, Let my people go, that they may hold a feast unto me in the wilderness. And Pharaoh said, Who is the LORD, that I should obey his voice to let Israel go? I know not the LORD, neither will I let Israel go. And they said, The God of the Hebrews hath met with us: let us go, we pray thee, three days&amp;rsquo; journey into the desert, and sacrifice unto the LORD our God; lest he fall upon us with pestilence, or with the sword.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 6</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/006/</guid><description>Then the LORD said unto Moses, Now shalt thou see what I will do to Pharaoh: for with a strong hand shall he let them go, and with a strong hand shall he drive them out of his land. And God spake unto Moses, and said unto him, I am the LORD: And I appeared unto Abraham, unto Isaac, and unto Jacob, by the name of God Almighty, but by my name JEHOVAH was I not known to them.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 7</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/007/</guid><description>And the LORD said unto Moses, See, I have made thee a god to Pharaoh: and Aaron thy brother shall be thy prophet. Thou shalt speak all that I command thee: and Aaron thy brother shall speak unto Pharaoh, that he send the children of Israel out of his land. And I will harden Pharaoh&amp;rsquo;s heart, and multiply my signs and my wonders in the land of Egypt. But Pharaoh shall not hearken unto you, that I may lay my hand upon Egypt, and bring forth mine armies, and my people the children of Israel, out of the land of Egypt by great judgments.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 8</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/008/</guid><description>And the LORD spake unto Moses, Go unto Pharaoh, and say unto him, Thus saith the LORD, Let my people go, that they may serve me. And if thou refuse to let them go, behold, I will smite all thy borders with frogs: And the river shall bring forth frogs abundantly, which shall go up and come into thine house, and into thy bedchamber, and upon thy bed, and into the house of thy servants, and upon thy people, and into thine ovens, and into thy kneadingtroughs: And the frogs shall come up both on thee, and upon thy people, and upon all thy servants.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 9</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/009/</guid><description>Then the LORD said unto Moses, Go in unto Pharaoh, and tell him, Thus saith the LORD God of the Hebrews, Let my people go, that they may serve me. For if thou refuse to let them go, and wilt hold them still, Behold, the hand of the LORD is upon thy cattle which is in the field, upon the horses, upon the asses, upon the camels, upon the oxen, and upon the sheep: there shall be a very grievous murrain.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 10</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/010/</guid><description>And the LORD said unto Moses, Go in unto Pharaoh: for I have hardened his heart, and the heart of his servants, that I might shew these my signs before him: And that thou mayest tell in the ears of thy son, and of thy son&amp;rsquo;s son, what things I have wrought in Egypt, and my signs which I have done among them; that ye may know how that I am the LORD.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 11</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/011/</guid><description>And the LORD said unto Moses, Yet will I bring one plague more upon Pharaoh, and upon Egypt; afterwards he will let you go hence: when he shall let you go, he shall surely thrust you out hence altogether. Speak now in the ears of the people, and let every man borrow of his neighbour, and every woman of her neighbour, jewels of silver, and jewels of gold. And the LORD gave the people favour in the sight of the Egyptians.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 12</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/012/</guid><description>And the LORD spake unto Moses and Aaron in the land of Egypt, saying, This month shall be unto you the beginning of months: it shall be the first month of the year to you. Speak ye unto all the congregation of Israel, saying, In the tenth day of this month they shall take to them every man a lamb, according to the house of their fathers, a lamb for an house: And if the household be too little for the lamb, let him and his neighbour next unto his house take it according to the number of the souls; every man according to his eating shall make your count for the lamb.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 13</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/013/</guid><description>And the LORD spake unto Moses, saying, Sanctify unto me all the firstborn, whatsoever openeth the womb among the children of Israel, both of man and of beast: it is mine. And Moses said unto the people, Remember this day, in which ye came out from Egypt, out of the house of bondage; for by strength of hand the LORD brought you out from this place: there shall no leavened bread be eaten.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 14</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/014/</guid><description>And the LORD spake unto Moses, saying, Speak unto the children of Israel, that they turn and encamp before Pihahiroth, between Migdol and the sea, over against Baalzephon: before it shall ye encamp by the sea. For Pharaoh will say of the children of Israel, They are entangled in the land, the wilderness hath shut them in. And I will harden Pharaoh&amp;rsquo;s heart, that he shall follow after them; and I will be honoured upon Pharaoh, and upon all his host; that the Egyptians may know that I am the LORD.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 15</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/015/</guid><description>Then sang Moses and the children of Israel this song unto the LORD, and spake, saying, I will sing unto the LORD, for he hath triumphed gloriously: the horse and his rider hath he thrown into the sea. The LORD is my strength and song, and he is become my salvation: he is my God, and I will prepare him an habitation; my father&amp;rsquo;s God, and I will exalt him.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 16</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/016/</guid><description>And they took their journey from Elim, and all the congregation of the children of Israel came unto the wilderness of Sin, which is between Elim and Sinai, on the fifteenth day of the second month after their departing out of the land of Egypt. And the whole congregation of the children of Israel murmured against Moses and Aaron in the wilderness: And the children of Israel said unto them, Would to God we had died by the hand of the LORD in the land of Egypt, when we sat by the flesh pots, and when we did eat bread to the full; for ye have brought us forth into this wilderness, to kill this whole assembly with hunger.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 17</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/017/</guid><description>And all the congregation of the children of Israel journeyed from the wilderness of Sin, after their journeys, according to the commandment of the LORD, and pitched in Rephidim: and there was no water for the people to drink. Wherefore the people did chide with Moses, and said, Give us water that we may drink. And Moses said unto them, Why chide ye with me? wherefore do ye tempt the LORD?</description></item><item><title>Chapter 18</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/018/</guid><description>When Jethro, the priest of Midian, Moses&amp;rsquo; father in law, heard of all that God had done for Moses, and for Israel his people, and that the LORD had brought Israel out of Egypt; Then Jethro, Moses&amp;rsquo; father in law, took Zipporah, Moses&amp;rsquo; wife, after he had sent her back, And her two sons; of which the name of the one was Gershom; for he said, I have been an alien in a strange land: And the name of the other was Eliezer; for the God of my father, said he, was mine help, and delivered me from the sword of Pharaoh: And Jethro, Moses&amp;rsquo; father in law, came with his sons and his wife unto Moses into the wilderness, where he encamped at the mount of God: And he said unto Moses, I thy father in law Jethro am come unto thee, and thy wife, and her two sons with her.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 19</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/019/</guid><description>In the third month, when the children of Israel were gone forth out of the land of Egypt, the same day came they into the wilderness of Sinai. For they were departed from Rephidim, and were come to the desert of Sinai, and had pitched in the wilderness; and there Israel camped before the mount. And Moses went up unto God, and the LORD called unto him out of the mountain, saying, Thus shalt thou say to the house of Jacob, and tell the children of Israel; Ye have seen what I did unto the Egyptians, and how I bare you on eagles&amp;rsquo; wings, and brought you unto myself.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 20</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/020/</guid><description>And God spake all these words, saying, I am the LORD thy God, which have brought thee out of the land of Egypt, out of the house of bondage. Thou shalt have no other gods before me. Thou shalt not make unto thee any graven image, or any likeness of any thing that is in heaven above, or that is in the earth beneath, or that is in the water under the earth: Thou shalt not bow down thyself to them, nor serve them: for I the LORD thy God am a jealous God, visiting the iniquity of the fathers upon the children unto the third and fourth generation of them that hate me; And shewing mercy unto thousands of them that love me, and keep my commandments.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 21</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/021/</guid><description>Now these are the judgments which thou shalt set before them. If thou buy an Hebrew servant, six years he shall serve: and in the seventh he shall go out free for nothing. If he came in by himself, he shall go out by himself: if he were married, then his wife shall go out with him. If his master have given him a wife, and she have born him sons or daughters; the wife and her children shall be her master&amp;rsquo;s, and he shall go out by himself.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 22</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/022/</guid><description>If a man shall steal an ox, or a sheep, and kill it, or sell it; he shall restore five oxen for an ox, and four sheep for a sheep. If a thief be found breaking up, and be smitten that he die, there shall no blood be shed for him. If the sun be risen upon him, there shall be blood shed for him; for he should make full restitution; if he have nothing, then he shall be sold for his theft.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 23</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/023/</guid><description>Thou shalt not raise a false report: put not thine hand with the wicked to be an unrighteous witness. Thou shalt not follow a multitude to do evil; neither shalt thou speak in a cause to decline after many to wrest judgment: Neither shalt thou countenance a poor man in his cause. If thou meet thine enemy&amp;rsquo;s ox or his ass going astray, thou shalt surely bring it back to him again.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 24</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/024/</guid><description>And he said unto Moses, Come up unto the LORD, thou, and Aaron, Nadab, and Abihu, and seventy of the elders of Israel; and worship ye afar off. And Moses alone shall come near the LORD: but they shall not come nigh; neither shall the people go up with him. And Moses came and told the people all the words of the LORD, and all the judgments: and all the people answered with one voice, and said, All the words which the LORD hath said will we do.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 25</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/025/</guid><description>And the LORD spake unto Moses, saying, Speak unto the children of Israel, that they bring me an offering: of every man that giveth it willingly with his heart ye shall take my offering. And this is the offering which ye shall take of them; gold, and silver, and brass, And blue, and purple, and scarlet, and fine linen, and goats&amp;rsquo; hair, And rams&amp;rsquo; skins dyed red, and badgers&amp;rsquo; skins, and shittim wood, Oil for the light, spices for anointing oil, and for sweet incense, Onyx stones, and stones to be set in the ephod, and in the breastplate.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 26</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/026/</guid><description>Moreover thou shalt make the tabernacle with ten curtains of fine twined linen, and blue, and purple, and scarlet: with cherubims of cunning work shalt thou make them. The length of one curtain shall be eight and twenty cubits, and the breadth of one curtain four cubits: and every one of the curtains shall have one measure. The five curtains shall be coupled together one to another; and other five curtains shall be coupled one to another.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 27</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/027/</guid><description>And thou shalt make an altar of shittim wood, five cubits long, and five cubits broad; the altar shall be foursquare: and the height thereof shall be three cubits. And thou shalt make the horns of it upon the four corners thereof: his horns shall be of the same: and thou shalt overlay it with brass. And thou shalt make his pans to receive his ashes, and his shovels, and his basons, and his fleshhooks, and his firepans: all the vessels thereof thou shalt make of brass.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 28</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/028/</guid><description>And take thou unto thee Aaron thy brother, and his sons with him, from among the children of Israel, that he may minister unto me in the priest&amp;rsquo;s office, even Aaron, Nadab and Abihu, Eleazar and Ithamar, Aaron&amp;rsquo;s sons. And thou shalt make holy garments for Aaron thy brother for glory and for beauty. And thou shalt speak unto all that are wise hearted, whom I have filled with the spirit of wisdom, that they may make Aaron&amp;rsquo;s garments to consecrate him, that he may minister unto me in the priest&amp;rsquo;s office.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 29</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/029/</guid><description>And this is the thing that thou shalt do unto them to hallow them, to minister unto me in the priest&amp;rsquo;s office: Take one young bullock, and two rams without blemish, And unleavened bread, and cakes unleavened tempered with oil, and wafers unleavened anointed with oil: of wheaten flour shalt thou make them. And thou shalt put them into one basket, and bring them in the basket, with the bullock and the two rams.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 30</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/030/</guid><description>And thou shalt make an altar to burn incense upon: of shittim wood shalt thou make it. A cubit shall be the length thereof, and a cubit the breadth thereof; foursquare shall it be: and two cubits shall be the height thereof: the horns thereof shall be of the same. And thou shalt overlay it with pure gold, the top thereof, and the sides thereof round about, and the horns thereof; and thou shalt make unto it a crown of gold round about.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 31</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/031/</guid><description>And the LORD spake unto Moses, saying, See, I have called by name Bezaleel the son of Uri, the son of Hur, of the tribe of Judah: And I have filled him with the spirit of God, in wisdom, and in understanding, and in knowledge, and in all manner of workmanship, To devise cunning works, to work in gold, and in silver, and in brass, And in cutting of stones, to set them, and in carving of timber, to work in all manner of workmanship.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 32</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/032/</guid><description>And when the people saw that Moses delayed to come down out of the mount, the people gathered themselves together unto Aaron, and said unto him, Up, make us gods, which shall go before us; for as for this Moses, the man that brought us up out of the land of Egypt, we wot not what is become of him. And Aaron said unto them, Break off the golden earrings, which are in the ears of your wives, of your sons, and of your daughters, and bring them unto me.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 33</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/033/</guid><description>And the LORD said unto Moses, Depart, and go up hence, thou and the people which thou hast brought up out of the land of Egypt, unto the land which I sware unto Abraham, to Isaac, and to Jacob, saying, Unto thy seed will I give it: And I will send an angel before thee; and I will drive out the Canaanite, the Amorite, and the Hittite, and the Perizzite, the Hivite, and the Jebusite: Unto a land flowing with milk and honey: for I will not go up in the midst of thee; for thou art a stiffnecked people: lest I consume thee in the way.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 34</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/034/</guid><description>And the LORD said unto Moses, Hew thee two tables of stone like unto the first: and I will write upon these tables the words that were in the first tables, which thou brakest. And be ready in the morning, and come up in the morning unto mount Sinai, and present thyself there to me in the top of the mount. And no man shall come up with thee, neither let any man be seen throughout all the mount; neither let the flocks nor herds feed before that mount.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 35</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/035/</guid><description>And Moses gathered all the congregation of the children of Israel together, and said unto them, These are the words which the LORD hath commanded, that ye should do them. Six days shall work be done, but on the seventh day there shall be to you an holy day, a sabbath of rest to the LORD: whosoever doeth work therein shall be put to death. Ye shall kindle no fire throughout your habitations upon the sabbath day.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 36</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/036/</guid><description>Then wrought Bezaleel and Aholiab, and every wise hearted man, in whom the LORD put wisdom and understanding to know how to work all manner of work for the service of the sanctuary, according to all that the LORD had commanded. And Moses called Bezaleel and Aholiab, and every wise hearted man, in whose heart the LORD had put wisdom, even every one whose heart stirred him up to come unto the work to do it: And they received of Moses all the offering, which the children of Israel had brought for the work of the service of the sanctuary, to make it withal.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 37</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/037/</guid><description>And Bezaleel made the ark of shittim wood: two cubits and a half was the length of it, and a cubit and a half the breadth of it, and a cubit and a half the height of it: And he overlaid it with pure gold within and without, and made a crown of gold to it round about. And he cast for it four rings of gold, to be set by the four corners of it; even two rings upon the one side of it, and two rings upon the other side of it.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 38</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/038/</guid><description>And he made the altar of burnt offering of shittim wood: five cubits was the length thereof, and five cubits the breadth thereof; it was foursquare; and three cubits the height thereof. And he made the horns thereof on the four corners of it; the horns thereof were of the same: and he overlaid it with brass. And he made all the vessels of the altar, the pots, and the shovels, and the basons, and the fleshhooks, and the firepans: all the vessels thereof made he of brass.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 39</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/039/</guid><description>And of the blue, and purple, and scarlet, they made cloths of service, to do service in the holy place, and made the holy garments for Aaron; as the LORD commanded Moses. And he made the ephod of gold, blue, and purple, and scarlet, and fine twined linen. And they did beat the gold into thin plates, and cut it into wires, to work it in the blue, and in the purple, and in the scarlet, and in the fine linen, with cunning work.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 40</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/exodus/040/</guid><description>And the LORD spake unto Moses, saying, On the first day of the first month shalt thou set up the tabernacle of the tent of the congregation. And thou shalt put therein the ark of the testimony, and cover the ark with the vail. And thou shalt bring in the table, and set in order the things that are to be set in order upon it; and thou shalt bring in the candlestick, and light the lamps thereof.</description></item></channel></rss>