<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Malachi on Bible</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/</link><description>Recent content in Malachi on Bible</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chapter 1</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/001/</guid><description>The burden of the word of the LORD to Israel by Malachi. I have loved you, saith the LORD. Yet ye say, Wherein hast thou loved us? Was not Esau Jacob&amp;rsquo;s brother? saith the LORD: yet I loved Jacob, And I hated Esau, and laid his mountains and his heritage waste for the dragons of the wilderness. Whereas Edom saith, We are impoverished, but we will return and build the desolate places; thus saith the LORD of hosts, They shall build, but I will throw down; and they shall call them, The border of wickedness, and, The people against whom the LORD hath indignation for ever.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 2</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/002/</guid><description>And now, O ye priests, this commandment is for you. If ye will not hear, and if ye will not lay it to heart, to give glory unto my name, saith the LORD of hosts, I will even send a curse upon you, and I will curse your blessings: yea, I have cursed them already, because ye do not lay it to heart. Behold, I will corrupt your seed, and spread dung upon your faces, even the dung of your solemn feasts; and one shall take you away with it.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 3</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/003/</guid><description>Behold, I will send my messenger, and he shall prepare the way before me: and the LORD, whom ye seek, shall suddenly come to his temple, even the messenger of the covenant, whom ye delight in: behold, he shall come, saith the LORD of hosts. But who may abide the day of his coming? and who shall stand when he appeareth? for he is like a refiner&amp;rsquo;s fire, and like fullers&amp;rsquo; soap: And he shall sit as a refiner and purifier of silver: and he shall purify the sons of Levi, and purge them as gold and silver, that they may offer unto the LORD an offering in righteousness.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 4</title><link>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.xizzhu.me/bible/kjv/malachi/004/</guid><description>For, behold, the day cometh, that shall burn as an oven; and all the proud, yea, and all that do wickedly, shall be stubble: and the day that cometh shall burn them up, saith the LORD of hosts, that it shall leave them neither root nor branch. But unto you that fear my name shall the Sun of righteousness arise with healing in his wings; and ye shall go forth, and grow up as calves of the stall.</description></item></channel></rss>